<content>
----- TEN CODES -----
10-1 - Roll call.
10-3 - Radio silence (for emergency transmissions).
10-4 - Affirmative/understood.
10-5 - Repeat last transmission.
10-6 - Disregard.
10-7 - Standby for further.
10-8 - Currently busy/unavailable.
10-9 - Currently busy/unavailable (detective covert operation).
10-14 - Requesting transportation (including location and target location).
10-15 - Suspects arrested (including number of suspects and target location i.e. SFPD HQ, SACF).
10-18 - Further assistance required (?).
10-20 - Geographical location.
10-21 - Report in your current status and location.
10-22 - Report in person (including target location).
10-27 - Switching radio channel.
10-40 - Large group/gathering of persons in area (four or above).
10-41 - Illegal activity.
10-43 - Wanted vehicle.
10-46 - Conduct a frisk or search.
10-50 - Out of vehicle for investigations.
10-55 - Traffic stop.
10-56 - Computer check (using the MDC).
10-57-VICTOR - Vehicle pursuit.
10-57-FOXTROT - Foot pursuit.
10-60 - Vehicle description(s) (including vehicle name, colours, number of occupants and obvious features such as number of doors or any vehicular damage).
10-61 - Person description(s) (including identity/race, attire, distinguishing features).
10-66 - Felony stop.
10-70 Code 1 - Officer in distress backup call request (lights or siren) - Respond in own time - if something comes up, Officer in distress should take priority.
10-70 Code 2 - Regular backup call request (no lights or siren, if something comes up, reroute to more important call)
10-70 Code 2-HIGH - Priority backup call request (no lights or siren, may be used at intersections/heavy traffic) - if something comes up, unless emergency, disregard it.
10-70 Code 3 - Emergency backup call request (lights and sirens) - Respond with lights and sirens - if something comes up, unless no other units responding to other call, should disregard.
10-71 - Medical assistance required.
10-75 - Officer in distress (unable to respond, in imminent danger).
10-78 - Special Weapons and Tactics required (state either non emergency or emergecy).
10-98 - No further assistance required.
10-99 - Situation concluded.

----- RESPONSE/JOB CODES -----
Code 0 - Urgent assistance required. All duty units must immediately drop what they are doing, be that booking a suspect or being engaged in an active pursuit, and attend the code 0 as soon as is practically possible.
Code 1 - Officer in distress. A heightened Code 3, but does not warrant the use of Code 0. 
Code 2 - Routine call (no lights or siren, obey road laws) - Respond in own time - may cancel response in reference to priority call comes up, handle it first.
Code 2 - HIGH Priority call (no lights or siren, may be used at intersections/heavy traffic) - may cancel response in reference to emergency call but should be avoided.
Code 3 - Emergency call (lights and sirens) - Respond with lights and sirens - if something comes up, unless no other units responding to other call, should disregard.
Code 4 - Available for calls/currently on patrol.
Code 5 - All available SWAT personnel report in on the radio.
Code 6 - Arrived on scene (include target location).
Code 7 - Meal break (for refreshments).

----- STATUS CODES -----
Status 1 - Reporting off duty.
Status 2 - Reporting on duty.

----- IDENTITY CODES -----
IC1 – White.
IC2 – Black.
IC3 – Hispanic.
IC4 – Middle Eastern.
IC5 – Asian.
IC6 – Unknown ethnicity.
</content>